http://www.drawtite.com/privacypolicy.html

Cart
Call Us Toll-Free!
1-877-HITCH-IT
(448-2448)
Shipping Locations: NY, FL, CA, MI, PA, TX, and Ontario, Canada
This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering
system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but
may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store
through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information
about your shopping experience. Please see the
Yahoo! Privacy Policy for more
information about how Yahoo! uses this information.
Plattsburgh Spring Inc.
www.877hitchit.com - www.drawtite.com
Our Commitment To Your PrivacyYour privacy is important to us.
To better protect your privacy the
following notice explains the information we collect, how it is used, how
it is safeguarded, and how to contact us if you have any concerns.
"We shred all Personal Information"
What Information Is Collected:
As part of the order process, the following information is collected
from shoppers:
Name Shipping/Billing Address Email address Phone number Credit/Debit
Card Information
How That Information Is Used:
We do not sell your data, and only use it for demographics and visitor
tracking purposes.
Contact Us:
Plattsburgh Spring, Inc.
9 South Peru Street
Plattsburgh, NY 12901
(518) 561-4182 Phone
(518) 562-0277 Fax
(877) Hitch-it (448-2448)
info@drawtite.com
The following information is from
Is Yahoo! Merchant Solutions secure?
Yahoo!
takes your security seriously and takes reasonable steps to protect
your information. No data transmission over the Internet or information
storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. The following
is a summary of the measures Yahoo! takes to protect your information
and descriptions of ways we implement these measures for different
types of information you may provide to us.
Security for buyers when ordering through a Yahoo! Store
The following is a description of steps Yahoo! takes to protect your
information from misuse when ordering through a Yahoo! Store.
Secure Socket Layer (SSL): Yahoo! Store uses SSL
(Secure Socket Layer) encryption when transmitting certain kinds of
information, such as financial services information or payment
information. An icon resembling a padlock is displayed on the bottom of
most browsers window during SSL transactions that involve credit cards
and other forms of payment. Any time a Yahoo! Store asks for a credit
card number during checkout for payment, it will be SSL encrypted. The
information you provide will be stored securely on our servers.
CISP Compliance:
Yahoo! Merchant Solutions is certified CISP-compliant. Created by Visa
and MasterCard, the Cardholder Information Security Program (CISP)
outlines a standard for security procedures for merchants and service
providers that store, process, or transmit cardholder data.
Learn more about CISP.
View the list of CISP-compliant service providers in PDF format
(Yahoo! Merchant Solutions appears on page 4).
Security for merchants when ordering Yahoo! services
Security Steps We Have Taken
Secure Socket Layer (SSL): Yahoo! uses SSL (Secure
Socket Layer) encryption when transmitting certain kinds of
information, such as financial services information or payment
information. An icon resembling a padlock is displayed on the bottom of
most browsers window during SSL transactions that involve credit cards
and other forms of payment. Any time Yahoo! asks you for a credit card
number on Yahoo! for payment or for verification purposes, it will be
SSL encrypted. The information you provide will be stored securely on
our servers. Once you choose to store or enter your credit card number
on Yahoo!, it will not be displayed back to you in its entirety when
you retrieve or edit it in the future. Instead of the entire number,
you will only see asterisks and either the first four digits or the
last four digits of your number.
Security Key: The
Yahoo! Security Key is an additional optional layer of security to
control access to sensitive information or services on Yahoo!. Users of
financial services such as Yahoo! Wallet, Yahoo! Bill Pay, and Yahoo!
Merchant Solutions are asked to create a security key during the
sign-up process or when you purchase certain services that require a
Yahoo! Wallet. Please note that the Security Key automatically "times
out" after an hour and requires the user to sign in again to access
Security Key protected areas.
Secure Storage: Yahoo!
maintains reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards
that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information
about you.
Vendors and Partners: Yahoo! works with vendors and partners to protect the security and privacy of user information.
Employee and Contractor Access to Information:
Yahoo! limits access to personal information about you to those
employees who we reasonably believe need to come into contact with that
information to provide products or services to you or in order to do
their jobs.
Education and Training for Employees: Yahoo! has implemented a company-wide education and training program about security that is required of every Yahoo! employee.
TowingTrailer HitchesFront Mount Trailer HitchesFifth Wheel Trailer HitchesGooseneck Trailer Hitch SystemsSway ControlsTow Bars and BracketsWeight Distribution SystemsTrailer Hitch AccessoriesAnti-Rattle DevicesBallsBall Mounts and AccessoriesFabrication PartsFront Mount Trailer Hitch AccessoriesLocksPintle Hooks & Lunette Rings Receiver Hitch Covers Replacement Hitch Bolt and Hardware Kit Electrical Wiring Including DiagramsT-One Wiring Harnesses (Plug in Wiring Connectors)5th Wheel and Gooseneck Wiring HarnessesBrake ControllersElectrical ConnectorsElectrical Mounting BracketsElectrical Wiring Testers ModulitesTaillight ConvertersWiring Adapters Wiring ComponentsWiring DiagramsVehicle AccessoriesBACKRACK Cab ProtectorsLeer Truck CapsLights and Electrical AccessoriesMirrors for TowingQuarantine Cargo NetsRampsTonneau CoversTransmission CoolersCargo ManagementCargo Carriers for 1 1/4" ReceiversCargo Carriers for 2" ReceiversRooftop CarriersRoof RacksCargo NetsCargo Carrier AccessoriesCargo BagsCargo Light KitsTow Straps and Tie DownsTruck or Van RacksBike RacksBike Carriers for 1 1/4" ReceiversBike Carriers for 2" ReceiversBike Carrier AccessoriesSuspensionWeight Distribution SystemsTimbren Suspension KitsTrailer PartsBearing KitsBrake AssembliesBreakaway Kits and Replacement PartsCouplersGooseneck Trailer PartsPintle Hooks & Lunette Rings Rack'Em Trailer AccessoriesTrailer JacksTrailer LocksTruck and Trailer LightingWheel ChocksWinches and AccessoriesSafety LightsBuyers ProductsNorth American Signal PSE Amber/Code 3 TowMate Wireless TowLights with Lifetime Warranty!Snow Removal & AccessoriesSnowDogg Snow PlowsPlow Replacement PartsTire ChainsSafety LightsDraw-Tite Corporate WebsiteDraw-Tite Corporate Website
Home
Site Map
About Us
Privacy Policy
FAQ
Contact Us
View Cart
Copyright 2019 Plattsburgh Spring, Inc. All Rights Reserved.Yahoo Store Web Design by Solid Cactus.
Product offering and prices listed on this website (www.drawtite.com/www.877hitchit.com) are limited to Internet and phone orders (1-877-HITCH-IT).
Product offering and/or prices may vary in our store.
Prices are also subject to change.
